First they destroyed a farm. Then they terrorized a town.
Now they're ready to do some REAL damage!
Critters 3 is a comedy, horror, science fiction
film directed by Kristine Peterson.
As fanged, furious furballs viciously invade an L.A.
apartment building and sink their teeth into the low-rent tenants, Josh leads the
battle to beat back the conniving critters and save the planet.
Annie, played by Aimee Brooks.
Clifford, played by John Calvin.
Marcia, played by Katherine Cortez.
Josh, played by Leonardo DiCaprio.
Frank Longo, played by Geoffrey Blake.
Rosalie, played by Diana Bellamy.
Critters 3 is a 1991 American science fiction comedy horror direct-to-video film and the
third installment of the Critters series, directed by Kristine Peterson.
The film stars Aimee Brooks, John Calvin, Katherine Cortez, Don
Keith Opper, and Leonardo DiCaprio in his film debut.
It was shot simultaneously (from February to July
1991) with its sequel, Critters 4.
Unlike the first two films, it does not take place in the town of Grover's Bend.
The film explores themes of fire, hologram,
sequel, alien, los angeles, california.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.